i teach the violin it's been over 15
years
and i love teaching i really believe
that every child i teach
can learn that they are not good at
violin
it's not that there are baddies i'm a
tough teacher i'm from france you know
in france it's very difficult
very difficult to make it through school
i'll give you an example
in america in many schools if a child's
of its grade is
d they still send him to the next grade
you know that
while in france if a child's average
grade is d
we send him to america
that's why i'm here
my my mom she saw my stand-up comedy for
the first time last year it was a big
moment in the family
she came backstage she had tears in her
eyes she hold my hands and she was like
you're not funny
my dad was very supportive he said no
matter what happened on stage and no
matter how difficult
don't ever use our family name
but i love teaching kids because
children are so honest
i teach this student jonathan every
monday very talented he sounds like this
[Music]
so i looked at the moment i'm like
did you drink during pregnancy
[Laughter]
and people have no more taste taste and
i can prove it you know like
today the music is so simple it's kind
of like having a conversation
with a toddler with five words five
notes ten notes max i give you an
example
one of my students got very famous
playing in the street
playing all those pop songs now she's a
very good violinist but she got famous
with pop songs
and if my student posts a video of her
playing despacito on youtube
she gets millions of views but if i play
a video of me playing a concerto
i get like one like
from my mom and then i get a comment
from my dad who is like have you seen
your student playing despacito on
youtube
stop using our family name
people have no more taste i can prove it
i'm gonna play something you guys don't
know
now i would like to play something that
everybody knows
it's two freaking notes
it's two notes i learned the violin for
30 years so you guys like
two notes
the worst is social media i can't stand
it by the way follow me at armando
violin comedy
[Music]
local man robs wendy's with alligator
we're the alligator boys now and the
baby sitting on the bank should be going
mom mom